JOSHUA ANTHONY A. DELGADO

Web Developer

+639103403757

O Brgy. Ibabang Dupay, Lucena City, Philippines



SUMMARY

A Web Developer proficient and have working experience in development, mainly HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Tailwind, Bootstrap, React framework, and WordPress with Elementor plugin. I bring web design concepts into a working and functional website. I develop and maintain user-facing features for web applications, ensure optimal performance across platforms, and optimize user experience on mobile and desktop.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Web Developer | Floor23 Digital LTD

Feb 2024 - Present

- Developed user-facing features for web applications aimed at innovation competitions and digital marketing campaigns.
- Ensures optimal performance and responsiveness across platforms, focusing on mobile and desktop compatibility.
- Collaborates with back-end developers and designers to ensure seamless integration and high-quality outputs.

Clerk/Encoder | Southern Luzon State University

Feb 2023 - Sept 2024

- Encode/Scans permanent records/documents to the Records Inventory System (RIS).
- Administer the Records Inventory System (RIS).
- · Provide assistance with the disposal of valueless records.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technical-Vocational in Teachers Education major in Computer Programming

2018 - 2022

Southern Luzon State University

- Major in Computer Programming.
- Graduated with a Latin Honor
- Thesis on "Mobile-Based Tabulation System on Scholastic Competition".

Information in Communications Technology major in Mobile App and Web

2016 - 2018

Development

STI College Lucena

Major in Mobile App and Web Development.

SKILLS

HTML5CSS

Bootstrap

React.Js

Canva Editor

JavaScript

Tailwind

Vue.Js

Microsoft Offices

MySQL

WordPressGitHub

PHP

• Adobe Premiere Pro

TRAININGS

Knowledge Transfer of Server and UTM Training (2022)

National Certificate ii in Computer System Servicing Training (2020) Post Evaluation: DICT-SLSU Cybersecurity Awareness Webinar (2020)

LICENSE / CERTIFICATES

License Professional Teacher - (LET) Passer (2023)

Certificate of Eligibility (Honor Graduate Eligibility) (2023)

National Certifi cate ii in Computer System Servicing Passer (2020)